<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <packageId>KyleGivler.BetterTradeColors</packageId>
  <name>Better Trade Colors</name>
  <author>Kyle Givler</author>
  <description>Better Trade Colors completely overhauls the visual clarity of the trading and caravan interfaces by color-coding items based on quality, durability, and condition. No more squinting or checking info cards to filter out junk—instantly parse everything at a glance.

Key Mechanics and Color Priorities:
- Tainted Apparel (Dim Red/Brown): Instantly catch items stripped from corpses before accidentally buying or selling them.
- Damaged Goods (Vibrant Magenta): Items under 50% durability are highlighted in sharp purple/magenta, alerting you to low hitpoint gear before making a bad trade.
- Quality Spectrum: Beautiful, non-clashing colors that map directly to the classic RimWorld quality tiers:
  * Awful / Poor (Greyscale)
  * Normal (White)
  * Good (Soft Green)
  * Excellent (Yellow / Gold)
  * Masterwork (True Orange)
  * Legendary (Cyan / Light Blue)

Technical Focus:
- Zero Bloat: Built entirely from scratch to avoid the heavy overhead of older UI color mods (looking at you, QualityColors).
- Ultra High-Performance: Uses lightweight Harmony prefixes on the core UI drawing pipeline. Completely avoids messy Regex replacements, string manipulation, or memory-heavy text caching (looking at you again, QualityColors).
- Conflict-Free: Safely modifies the rendering colors without altering underlying data structures, maintaining robust compatibility with major UI overhaul mods.

Plans:
I wrote this mod because I was unhappy with the architectural mess of QualityColors. While this iteration doesn't do all of the same global features, it provides a strictly better, lightweight foundation for exactly what I need.
- Future updates will include customizable colors via a mod menu.
- Customizable HP percentages for damaged goods.

</description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modVersion>1.0.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>